(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
(شاهد على www.dramacool.club دعم الإدارة)
I haven't seen him
لم أره
since graduation.
منذ التخرج.
When I saw him today,
عندما رأيته اليوم،
I was so nervous
كنت متوتراً للغاية
that I didn't even call his name.
أنني لم أنادِ باسمه حتى.
Senior.
كبير.
Honey.
عسل.
Don't you want to introduce him?
ألا تريد أن تقدمه؟
I don't need to use marriage
لست بحاجة إلى استخدام الزواج
as a lowly means.
كوسيلة متواضعة.
I told you.
أخبرتك.
You can only be mine.
لا يمكن أن تكوني إلا لي.
You look like him the most.
أنت تشبهه أكثر من غيرك.
Unfortunately,
للأسف،
you are not as fierce as him.
أنت لستَ شرساً مثله.
Now,
الآن،
you look like him.
أنت تشبهه.
Don't forget
لا تنسى
who gave you the life you have now.
من الذي منحك الحياة التي تعيشها الآن؟
Be a good substitute for him.
كن بديلاً جيداً له.
That's the only way you can repay me.
هذه هي الطريقة الوحيدة التي يمكنك بها رد الجميل لي.
Vivi.
أنت حي.
Senior.
كبير.
It's been a long time
لقد مر وقت طويل
called me that for a long time.
لقد ناداني بذلك لفترة طويلة.
Senior,
كبير،
I just can't remember
لا أستطيع أن أتذكر
how we got together.
كيف التقينا.
Have some water.
اشرب بعض الماء.
We...
نحن...
You...
أنت...
What you're doing is illegal.
ما تفعله غير قانوني.
I'm just curious
أنا فضولي فقط
if people will still be stubborn
إذا ظل الناس عنيدين
when they are dying.
عندما يحتضرون.
So you're such a curious person.
إذن أنت شخص فضولي للغاية.
Am I a suicide or not?
هل أنا شخص انتحاري أم لا؟
It's all my fault.
كل هذا خطأي.
I knew you were sad and out of control because of your parents,
كنت أعلم أنك حزين وفاقد للسيطرة بسبب والديك،
but I didn't take care of you.
لكنني لم أعتني بك.
Miss Lan.
الآنسة لان.
You... know me?
أنت تعرفني؟
Of course. You disappeared at that time,
بالطبع. لقد اختفيت في ذلك الوقت.
and the hospital has been looking for you for a long time.
والمستشفى يبحث عنك منذ فترة طويلة.
Disappeared? Yes.
اختفوا؟ نعم.
You just disappeared.
لقد اختفيت فجأة.
I always remember the scene of being pushed down the stairs.
أتذكر دائماً مشهد دفعي من أعلى الدرج.
Did you do that to me?
هل فعلت ذلك بي؟
In your eyes,
في عينيك،
am I really
هل أنا حقاً
such an unforgivable murderer?
قاتل لا يغتفر له مثل هذا؟
Am I?
هل أنا كذلك؟
We are husband and wife.
نحن زوج وزوجة.
If I kill you,
إذا قتلتك،
I will be the prime suspect.
سأكون المشتبه به الرئيسي.
There is no news of our marriage.
لا توجد أي أخبار عن زواجنا.
If I'm not wrong,
إن لم أكن مخطئاً،
no one knows
لا أحد يعلم
we're married, right?
نحن متزوجان، أليس كذلك؟
Don't you get it?
ألا تفهم ذلك؟
I'm protecting you.
أنا أحميك.
My parents died on the day
توفي والداي في ذلك اليوم
we got married.
تزوجنا.
You suspected
كنت تشك
I killed your family.
لقد قتلت عائلتك.
This is your last chance to confess.
هذه فرصتك الأخيرة للاعتراف.
What era is this?
في أي عصر هذا؟
You're still using torture to extract confessions.
ما زلت تستخدم التعذيب لانتزاع الاعترافات.
But
لكن
I like your little quirks.
أحب عاداتك الصغيرة الغريبة.
I had nothing to do with what happened back then.
لم يكن لي أي علاقة بما حدث في ذلك الوقت.
But I woke up
لكنني استيقظت
in your house.
في منزلك.
Why did the hospital say I was missing?
لماذا قال المستشفى إنني مفقود؟
And why did Blue Crane
ولماذا فعلت بلو كرين ذلك؟
suddenly disappear?
يختفي فجأة؟
Why did you marry me?
لماذا تزوجتني؟
Is it because of
هل السبب هو
the land of Blue Crane Resort?
أرض منتجع بلو كرين؟
Is that how you think of me?
هل هذه هي الطريقة التي تفكر بها بي؟
Lanhe Group
مجموعة لانهي
has been on a decline
وقد شهدت تراجعاً
since your parents passed away.
منذ وفاة والديك.
While Lin Group is soaring.
بينما تشهد مجموعة لين ازدهاراً كبيراً.
If it weren't for helping you keep Lanhe,
لولا مساعدتك في الاحتفاظ بـ "لانهي"،
I wouldn't bother
لن أكلف نفسي عناء ذلك
with charity work.
من خلال العمل الخيري.
My feelings for you
مشاعري تجاهك
are genuine.
أصلية.
I admit,
أعترف بذلك،
I initially approached you
لقد تواصلت معك في البداية
because you were the sole heir of Lanhe.
لأنك كنت الوريث الوحيد لـ لانهي.
That's why on our wedding day,
لهذا السبب في يوم زفافنا،
once you got the legal inheritance,
بمجرد حصولك على الميراث القانوني،
you tried to kill me.
لقد حاولت قتلي.
No.
لا.
But after getting to know you,
لكن بعد التعرف عليك،
I felt
شعرت
your kindness and gentleness.
لطفك ولطفك.
I truly fell in love with you.
لقد وقعت في حبك حقاً.
In that case,
في هذه الحالة،
for me,
لي،
and for your love,
ومن أجل حبك،
just die quietly.
موت بهدوء.
Don't you want to know what happened
ألا تريد أن تعرف ما حدث؟
during the year you lost your memory?
خلال السنة التي فقدت فيها ذاكرتك؟
Let me go,
دعني أذهب،
and I'll tell you everything.
وسأخبرك بكل شيء.
I suddenly realize
أدركت فجأة
I've been too kind to you.
لقد كنت لطيفاً معك أكثر من اللازم.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
I can tell you everything.
أستطيع أن أخبرك بكل شيء.
No need.
لا حاجة.
If you won't tell me,
إذا لم تخبرني،
someone else will.
شخص آخر سيفعل ذلك.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
Lan Hewei! I'm warning you,
لان هيوي! أنا أحذرك،
don't mess around!
لا تعبث!
Lan Hewei!
لان هيوي!
Are you serious?
هل أنت جاد؟
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
Give me a location!
أعطني موقعاً!
Go to the next room,
اذهب إلى الغرفة التالية،
don't come out without my permission!
لا تخرج بدون إذني!
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Lan Hewei, come here.
لان هيوي، تعال هنا.
I'll tell you everything.
سأخبرك بكل شيء.
How come it's you?
كيف حدث ذلك معك؟
You're snooping through his phone?
هل تتجسسين على هاتفه؟
Miss Zhu, how dare you
يا آنسة تشو، كيف تجرؤين؟
send flirtatious messages to my husband?
هل يمكنني إرسال رسائل غزلية إلى زوجي؟
And you're worried I might see them?
وهل أنت قلق من أن أراهم؟
I have something
لدي شيء ما
I want to discuss with you.
أريد أن أناقش الأمر معك.
I want to know everything that happened
أريد أن أعرف كل ما حدث
that happened to the Lan family.
هذا ما حدث لعائلة لان.
What does the Lan family's business
ما هو نشاط عائلة لان التجاري؟
have to do with me?
هل له علاقة بي؟
You're so close to my husband.
أنتِ قريبة جداً من زوجي.
You must be in contact with him often.
يجب أن تكون على اتصال به بشكل متكرر.
So, can you still reach him
هل ما زال بإمكانك الوصول إليه؟
starting this afternoon?
ابتداءً من بعد ظهر اليوم؟
What did you do to him?
ماذا فعلت به؟
Can we talk now?
هل يمكننا التحدث الآن؟
Tell me everything you know.
أخبرني بكل ما تعرفه.
It seems
يبدو
you and your husband's
أنتِ وزوجكِ
don't have a good relationship.
لا تربطنا علاقة جيدة.
Otherwise, he would have told you.
وإلا لكان أخبرك.
It seems that you
يبدو أنك
don't care about his life and death.
لا أهتم بحياته وموته.
Lan Hewei,
لان هيوي,
I'm not in a hurry.
لستُ في عجلة من أمري.
But he
لكنه
may not be able to wait that long.
قد لا يكون بالإمكان الانتظار كل هذه المدة.
If anything happens to him,
إذا حدث له أي مكروه،
I'll make you pay.
سأجعلك تدفع الثمن.
He escaped so quickly.
لقد هرب بسرعة كبيرة.
Let go of me.
اتركني وشأني.
I'll take you to him.
سآخذك إليه.
I don't need it. Let go of me.
لستُ بحاجةٍ إليه. دعني وشأني.
Don't move.
لا تتحرك. اتركني.
The locator must be malfunctioning.
لا بد أن جهاز تحديد الموقع معطل.
What is he doing here?
ماذا يفعل هنا؟
The scenery here is nice.
المناظر الطبيعية هنا جميلة.
It's a perfect place for murder,
إنه مكان مثالي للقتل،
dumping bodies, and staging accidents.
إلقاء الجثث، وتدبير الحوادث.
I didn't expect you're still alive.
لم أتوقع أنك ما زلت على قيد الحياة.
What?
ماذا؟
You seem disappointed,
يبدو أنك تشعر بخيبة أمل،
my dear brother.
أخي العزيز.
If the president of Lin Group
إذا كان رئيس مجموعة لين
died in a fall accident,
توفي في حادث سقوط،
everything of yours would be mine.
كل ما تملكه سيكون ملكي.
What the hell is this place?
ما هذا المكان بحق الجحيم؟
Lin Moqing,
لين موكينج,
as long as you leave Haicheng,
طالما أنك تغادر هايتشنغ،
I'll make sure you live a rich life.
سأحرص على أن تعيش حياة ثرية.
Since you care about me so much,
بما أنك تهتم بي كثيراً،
why don't you
لماذا لا تفعل ذلك؟
let me back to the Lin Group?
هل تسمح لي بالعودة إلى مجموعة لين؟
You disappeared for so many years.
لقد اختفيت لسنوات عديدة.
I even set up a tombstone for you.
بل إنني نصبتُ لك شاهد قبر.
Now you suddenly appear.
والآن تظهر فجأة.
It's embarrassing for everyone.
إنه أمر محرج للجميع.
You can stand here
يمكنك الوقوف هنا
is the greatest mercy I can show you.
إنها أعظم رحمة يمكنني أن أقدمها لك.
Who is it?
من هذا؟
Zhu Wenjie.
تشو ون جيه.